Guide to the William T. Grant Foundation records FA004
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 1940-1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; 3; Tavistock Institute of Human Relations; Spock, Benjamin (1903-1998); Freud, Anna (1895-1982); Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic; Goodall, Jane (1934); 96.9 Cubic Feet 246 letter document boxes, 5 legal document boxes, 4 half-legal boxes, 1 card f
  - Grant files, 1970s - 1990s, bulk 1980s; 1980-1989; B
    - Queens County Art & Cultural Center - Reports - Janet Schneider (84-0988-84), 1985-1986 (Box 204, Folder 2821)
    - Queens Village Committee for Mental Health for Jamaica Community - Administration - Thomas White; Imani Kazana (85-1024-85), 1985 (Box 204, Folder 2822)
    - Queens Village Committee for Mental Health for Jamaica Community - Application - Thomas White; Imani Kazana (85-1024-85), 1985 (Box 204, Folder 2822)
    - Queens Village Committee for Mental Health for Jamaica Community - Finance - Thomas White; Imani Kazana (85-1024-85), 1986-1987 (Box 204, Folder 2824)
    - Queens Village Committee for Mental Health for Jamaica Community - Reports - Thomas White; Imani Kazana (85-1024-85), 1987 (Box 204, Folder 2825)
    - Radcliffe College - Administration - Sally Powers (83-0873-00), 1983-1985 (Box 205, Folder 2826)
    - Radcliffe College - Application - Sally Powers (83-0873-00), 1982-1986 (Box 205, Folder 2827)
    - Radcliffe College - Final Report - Sally Powers (83-0873-00), 1985-1986 (Box 205, Folder 2828-2830)
    - Radcliffe College - Finance - Sally Powers (83-0873-00), 1984-1986 (Box 205, Folder 2831)
    - Radcliffe College - Reports - Sally Powers (83-0873-00), 1986-1990 (Box 205, Folder 2832)
    - Radcliffe College - Sally Powers (83-0873-00), 1983 (Box 205, Folder 2833)
    - Rehabilitation Through Photography - Administration - Mr. B. Pendleton Rogers (82-0829-00), 1982-1986 (Box 205, Folder 2834)
    - Rehabilitation Through Photography - Application - Mr. B. Pendleton Rogers (82-0829-00), 1982-1984 (Box 205, Folder 2835)
    - Rehabilitation Through Photography - Finance - Mr. B. Pendleton Rogers (82-0829-00), 1983 (Box 205, Folder 2836)
    - Rehabilitation Through Photography - Reports - Mr. B. Pendleton Rogers (82-0829-00), 1983-1986 (Box 205, Folder 2837)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - Paul D. Trautmen, M.D. (83-0874-00), 1983-1986 (Box 206, Folder 2838)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - Paul D. Trautmen, M.D. (83-0874-00), 1982-1986 (Box 206, Folder 2838-2841)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Final Report - Paul D. Trautmen, M.D. (83-0874-00), 1987-1988 (Box 206, Folder 2842)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - Paul D. Trautmen, M.D. (83-0874-00), 1985-1986 (Box 206, Folder 2843)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Reports - Paul Trautman - (83-0874-00), 1984-1988 (Box 206, Folder 2844-2846)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Restricted - Paul Trautman (83-0874-00), 1983 (Box 206, Folder 2847)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (86-1105-86), 1986-1987 (Box 207, Folder 2848)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (86-1105-86), 1986-1987 (Box 207, Folder 2849)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Final Report - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (86-1105-86), 1987-1988 (Box 207, Folder 2850)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (86-1105-86), 1987 (Box 207, Folder 2851)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (84-0944-84), 1984-1985 (Box 207, Folder 2852)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (84-0944-84), 1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 2853)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Final Report - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (84-0944-84), 1985 (Box 207, Folder 2854)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - Patricia R. Cohen, Ph.D. (84-0944-84), 1985 (Box 207, Folder 2855)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D.; Heino F. L. Meyer (87-0982-84), 1984-1987 (Box 207, Folder 2856)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D., Heino F. L. Meyer (87-0982-84), 1984-1989 (Box 207, Folder 2857)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Final Report - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D., Heino F. L. Meyer (87-0982-84), 1985-1989 (Box 207, Folder 2858)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D., Heino F. L. Meyer (87-0982-84), 1985-1989 (Box 207, Folder 2859)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Reports - Anke A. Ehrhardt, Ph.D., Heino F. L. Meyer (87-0982-84), 1985-1989 (Box 207, Folder 2860)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - William H. Kaplan (83-0915-00), 1983-1989 (Box 207, Folder 2861)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - William H. Kaplan (83-0915-00), 1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 2862)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Final Report - William H. Kaplan (83-0915-00), 1989 (Box 207, Folder 2863)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - William H. Kaplan (83-0915-00), 1983-1985 (Box 207, Folder 2864)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Reports, Publications - William H. Kaplan (83-0915-00), 1983-1988 (Box 207, Folder 2865)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - L. Erlenmeyer-Kimling, Ph.D. (83-0918-00), 1983-1986 (Box 207, Folder 2866)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - L. Erlenmeyer-Kimling, Ph.D. (83-0918-00), 1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 2867)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - L. Erlenmeyer-Kimling, Ph.D. (83-0918-00), 1983-1986 (Box 207, Folder 2868)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Reports - L. Erlenmeyer-Kimling, Ph.D. (83-0918-00), 1986 (Box 207, Folder 2869)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - Richard Pleak, M.D. (87-1132-87), 1987-1988 (Box 207, Folder 2870)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - Richard Pleak, M.D. (87-1132-87), 1986-1988 (Box 207, Folder 2871)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Administration - Richard Pleak, M.D. (87-1132-87), 1984-1985 (Box 207, Folder 2872)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Application - Richard Pleak, M.D. (87-1132-87), 1984-1985 (Box 207, Folder 2873)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Final Report - Richard Pleak, M.D. (87-1132-87), 1986 (Box 207, Folder 2874)
    - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene - Finance - Richard Pleak, M.D. (87-1132-87), 1987-1989 (Box 207, Folder 2875)
    - Riverdale Community Center - Administration - Ferne Laude (85-1041-85), 1985-1986 (Box 208, Folder 2876)
    - Riverdale Community Center - Application - Ferne Laude (85-1041-85), 1985-1986 (Box 208, Folder 2877)
    - Riverdale Community Center - Finance - Ferne Laude (85-1041-85), 1986 (Box 208, Folder 2878)
    - Riverdale Community Center - Reports - Ferne Laude (85-1041-85), 1986 (Box 208, Folder 2879)
      See Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 284, folder 3592.
    - University of Rochester Medical Center - Administration - O.J. Sahler, M.D. (85-1037-85), 1985-1987 (Box 208, Folder 2880)
    - University of Rochester Medical Center - Application - O.J. Sahler, M.D. (85-1037-85), 1985-1986 (Box 208, Folder 2881)
    - University of Rochester Medical Center - Final Report - O.J. Sahler, M.D. (85-1037-85), 1987 (Box 208, Folder 2882)
    - University of Rochester Medical Center - Finance - O.J. Sahler, M.D. (85-1037-85), 1986-1987 (Box 208, Folder 2883)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Administration - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1987 (Box 208, Folder 2884)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Application - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1987-1988 (Box 208, Folder 2885)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Finance - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1987-1989 (Box 208, Folder 2886)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Reports - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1989 (Box 208, Folder 2887)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Administration - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1982-1985 (Box 208, Folder 2888)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Application - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 2889)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Final Report - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1983-1988 (Box 208, Folder 2890-2891)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Finance - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1983-1984 (Box 208, Folder 2892)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - Reports - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1983-1988 (Box 208, Folder 2893)
    - Rutgers State University of New Jersey - David Mechanic, Ph.D. (87-1165-87), 1982 (Box 208, Folder 2894)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Administration - Ms. Jane A. Hurst (82-0841-00), 1982 (Box 208, Folder 2895)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Application - Ms. Jane A. Hurst (82-0841-00), 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 2896)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Final Report - Ms. Jane A. Hurst (82-0841-00), 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 2897)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Finance - Ms. Jane A. Hurst (82-0841-00), 1983 (Box 208, Folder 2898)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Administration - Bruce Miller (83-0910-00), 1983 (Box 209, Folder 2899)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Application - Bruce Miller (83-0910-00), 1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 2900)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Finance - Bruce Miller (83-0910-00), 1983-1988 (Box 209, Folder 2901)
    - Saint Clare's Hospital - Report - Bruce Miller (83-0910-00), 1983 (Box 209, Folder 2902)
    - Saint Christopher's Home - Administration - Robert J. McMahon (83-0921-00), 1983 (Box 209, Folder 2903)
    - Saint Christopher's Home - Application - Robert J. McMahon (83-0921-00), 1983-1986 (Box 209, Folder 2904)
    - Saint Christopher's Home - Finance - Robert J. McMahon (83-0921-00), 1985 (Box 209, Folder 2905)
    - Saint Christopher's Home - Reports - Robert J. McMahon (83-0921-00), 1985-1986 (Box 209, Folder 2906)
    - Saint Joseph's Indian School - Administration - Dr. Cyrin F. Maus (84-0967-84), 1986 (Box 209, Folder 2907)
    - Saint Joseph's Indian School - Application - Dr. Cyrin F. Maus (84-0967-84), 1984 (Box 209, Folder 2908)
    - Saint Joseph's Indian School - Finance - Dr. Cyrin F. Maus (84-0967-84), 1986 (Box 209, Folder 2909)
    - Saint Joseph's Indian School - Reports - Dr. Cyrin F. Maus (84-0967-84), 1986 (Box 209, Folder 2910)
    - Scan N.Y. Volunteer Parent-Aides - Administration - Arlene Koeppel (83-0936-00), 1983-1986 (Box 209, Folder 2911)
    - Scan N.Y. Volunteer Parent-Aides - Application - Arlene Koeppel (83-0936-00), 1983-1987 (Box 209, Folder 2912)
    - Scan N.Y. Volunteer Parent-Aides - Finance - Arlene Koeppel (83-0936-00), 1985-1986 (Box 209, Folder 2913)
    - Scan N.Y. Volunteer Parent-Aides - Reports - Arlene Koeppel (83-0936-00), 1985-1989 (Box 209, Folder 2914)
    - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore - Administration - Evan Charney; Suezanne T. Orr (82-0838-00), 1982-1987 (Box 209, Folder 2915)
    - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore - Application - Evan Charney; Suezanne T. Orr (82-0838-00), 1983-1984 (Box 209, Folder 2916)
    - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore - Finance - Evan Charney; Suezanne T. Orr (82-0838-00), 1984-1987 (Box 209, Folder 2917)
    - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore - Reports - Evan Charney; Suezanne T. Orr (82-0838-00), 1983-1989 (Box 210, Folder 2918)
    - Social Science Research Council - Administration - Kenneth Prewitt, Ph.D. (83-0905-00), 1983 (Box 210, Folder 2919)
    - Social Science Research Council - Application - Kenneth Prewitt, Ph.D. (83-0905-00), 1983-1985 (Box 210, Folder 2920)
    - Social Science Research Council - Final Report - Kenneth Prewitt, Ph.D. (83-0905-00), 1983 (Box 210, Folder 2921-2922)
    - Social Science Research Council - Finance - Kenneth Prewitt, Ph.D. (83-0905-00), 1984 (Box 210, Folder 2923)
    - Social Science Research Council - Reports - Kenneth Prewitt, Ph.D. (83-0905-00), 1985 (Box 210, Folder 2924)
    - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore - Evan Charney; Suezanne T. Orr (82-0838-00), 1982 (Box 210, Folder 2925)
    - Society for Research in Child Development - Administration - Barbara A. Everett, Ph.D. (85-1004-85), 1984-1987 (Box 210, Folder 2926)
    - Society for Research in Child Development - Application - Barbara A. Everett, Ph.D. (85-1004-85), 1984-1986 (Box 210, Folder 2927)
    - Society for Research in Child Development - Finance - Barbara A. Everett, Ph.D. (85-1004-85), 1987 (Box 210, Folder 2928)
    - Society for Research in Child Development - Reports - Barbara A. Everett, Ph.D. (85-1004-85), 1987 (Box 210, Folder 2929)
    - University of Southern California - Administration - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1983-1989 (Box 210, Folder 2930)
    - University of Southern California - Application - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1983 (Box 210, Folder 2931)
    - University of Southern California - Application - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1983 (Box 211, Folder 2932)
    - University of Southern California - Final Report - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1985-1987 (Box 211, Folder 2933)
    - University of Southern California - Finance - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1984-1985 (Box 211, Folder 2934)
    - University of Southern California - Reports - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1986-1987 (Box 211, Folder 2935)
    - University of Southern California - Carl Anderson Johnson, Ph.D. (83-0924-00), 1983 (Box 211, Folder 2936)
    - Stanford University - Administration - Eleanor Maccoby, Ph.D. (85-0932-83), 1983-1985 (Box 211, Folder 2937)
    - Stanford University - Application - Eleanor Maccoby, Ph.D. (85-0932-83), 1983-1985 (Box 211, Folder 2938)
    - Stanford University - Finance - Eleanor Maccoby, Ph.D. (85-0932-83), 1984-1985 (Box 211, Folder 2939)
    - Stanford University - Report - Eleanor Maccoby, Ph.D. (85-0932-83), 1986 (Box 211, Folder 2940)
    - State Communities Aid Association - Administration - Thomas M. McKenna (84-0990-84), 1984-1986 (Box 211, Folder 2941)
    - State Communities Aid Association - Application - Thomas M. McKenna (84-0990-84), 1985 (Box 211, Folder 2942)
    - State Communities Aid Association - Finance - Thomas M. McKenna (84-0990-84), 1985-1986 (Box 211, Folder 2943)
    - State Communities Aid Association - Report - Thomas M. McKenna (84-0990-84), 1986 (Box 211, Folder 2944)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Application - Wendy K. Silverman, Ph.D. (83-0890-00), 1983-1984 (Box 211, Folder 2945)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Administration - Wendy K. Silverman, Ph.D. (83-0890-00), 1983-1986 (Box 211, Folder 2946)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Bibliography - Wendy K. Silverman, Ph.D. (83-0890-00), 1983-1986 (Box 211, Folder 2947)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Finance - Wendy K. Silverman, Ph.D. (83-0890-00), 1983-1986 (Box 211, Folder 2948)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Reports - Wendy K. Silverman, Ph.D. (83-0890-00), 1985 (Box 211, Folder 2949)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Administration - Frank Andraski (84-0993-84), 1984 (Box 212, Folder 2950)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Application - Frank Andraski (84-0993-84), 1984-1989 (Box 212, Folder 2951)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Final Report - Frank Andraski (84-0993-84), 1986 (Box 212, Folder 2952)
    - State University of New York, Albany - Finance - Frank Andraski (84-0993-84), 1985-1986 (Box 212, Folder 2953)
    - Student National Medical Association - Administration - James L. Loving, Jr. (83-0806-82), 1982-1987 (Box 212, Folder 2954)
    - Student National Medical Association - Application - James L. Loving, Jr. (83-0806-82), 1982-1983 (Box 212, Folder 2955)
    - Student National Medical Association - Finance - James L. Loving, Jr. (83-0806-82), 1982-1983 (Box 212, Folder 2956)
    - Student National Medical Association - Reports - James L. Loving, Jr. (83-0806-82), 1982-1986 (Box 212, Folder 2957)
    - Talbot Perkins Children's Service - Administration - William H. Mull, ACSW (82-0858-00), 1982 (Box 212, Folder 2958)
    - Talbot Perkins Children's Service - Application - William H. Mull, ACSW (82-0858-00), 1982-1983 (Box 212, Folder 2959)
    - Talbot Perkins Children's Service - Finance - William H. Mull, ACSW (82-0858-00), 1982 (Box 212, Folder 2960)
    - Talbot Perkins Children's Service - Reports - William H. Mull, ACSW (82-0858-00), 1984 (Box 212, Folder 2961)
    - University of Tennessee - Administration - Bruce S. Alpert, M.D. (83-0900-00), 1982-1984 (Box 212, Folder 2962)
    - University of Tennessee - Application - Bruce S. Alpert, M.D. (83-0900-00), 1983 (Box 212, Folder 2963)
    - University of Tennessee - Finance - Bruce S. Alpert, M.D. (83-0900-00), 1983-1986 (Box 212, Folder 2964)
    - University of Tennessee - General Correspondence - Bruce S. Alpert, M.D. (83-0900-00), 1983-1986 (Box 212, Folder 2965)
    - University of Tennessee - Reports - Bruce S. Alpert, M.D. (83-0900-00), 1985-1986 (Box 212, Folder 2966)
    - University of Texas at Austin - Application - Norval D. Glenn, Ph.D. (81-0755-81), 1984 (Box 212, Folder 2967)
    - University of Texas at Austin - Finance - Norval D. Glenn, Ph.D. (81-0755-81), 1984 (Box 212, Folder 2968)
    - University of Texas at Austin - Reports, Publications - Norval D. Glenn, Ph.D. (81-0755-81), 1984 (Box 212, Folder 2969)
    - University of Texas Medical Branch - Administration - Susan Gilman Brink, Ph.D. (86-1083-86), 1986-1987 (Box 212, Folder 2970)
    - University of Texas Medical Branch - Application - Susan Gilman Brink, Ph.D. (86-1083-86), 1986 (Box 213, Folder 2971)
    - University of Texas Medical Branch - Final Report - Susan Gilman Brink, Ph.D. (86-1083-86), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2972)
    - University of Texas Medical Branch - Finance - Susan Gilman Brink, Ph.D. (86-1083-86), 1986-1987 (Box 213, Folder 2973)
    - University of Texas Medical Branch - Susan Gilman Brink, Ph.D. (86-1083-86), 1986 (Box 213, Folder 2974)
    - Trail Blazer Camps - Administration - Jane Brokaw, C.C.D. (83-0901-00), 1983 (Box 213, Folder 2975)
    - Trail Blazer Camps - Application - Jane Brokaw, C.C.D. (83-0901-00), 1983 (Box 213, Folder 2976)
    - Trail Blazer Camps - Finance - Jane Brokaw, C.C.D. (83-0901-00), 1983 (Box 213, Folder 2977)
    - Trail Blazer Camps - Reports - Jane Brokaw, C.C.D. (83-0901-00), 1983-1985 (Box 213, Folder 2978)
    - Twin Cities Public Television - Administration - John Merrow (84-0965-84), 1984-1985 (Box 213, Folder 2979)
    - Twin Cities Public Television - Application - John Merrow (84-0965-84), 1984 (Box 213, Folder 2980)
    - Twin Cities Public Television - Finance - John Merrow (84-0965-84), 1985 (Box 213, Folder 2981)
    - Twin Cities Public Television - Reports - John Merrow (84-0965-84), 1984-1985 (Box 213, Folder 2982)
    - Union Settlement Association - Administration - Eugene Sklar (83-0937-00), 1983-1985 (Box 213, Folder 2983)
    - Union Settlement Association - Application - Eugene Sklar (83-0937-00), 1983-1985 (Box 213, Folder 2984)
    - Union Settlement Association - Finance - Eugene Sklar (83-0937-00), 1983-1985 (Box 213, Folder 2985)
    - Union Settlement Association - Reports - Eugene Sklar (83-0937-00), 1985 (Box 213, Folder 2986)
    - Union Settlement Association - Administration - Eugene Sklar (87-1142-87), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2987)
    - Union Settlement Association - Application - Eugene Sklar (87-1142-87), 1987-1988 (Box 213, Folder 2988)
    - Union Settlement Association - Final Report - Eugene Sklar (87-1142-87), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 2989)
    - Union Settlement Association - Finance - Eugene Sklar (87-1142-87), 1988 (Box 213, Folder 2990)
    - Union Settlement Association - Reports, Publications - Eugene Sklar (87-1142-87), 1994 (Box 213, Folder 2991)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, New York - Administration - Joseph Jenkins; Celine Marcus (86-1117-86), 1986-1987 (Box 213, Folder 2992)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, New York - Application - Joseph Jenkins; Celine Marcus (86-1117-86), 1986-1988 (Box 213, Folder 2993)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, New York - Final Report - Joseph Jenkins; Celine Marcus (86-1117-86), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2994)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, New York - Finance - Joseph Jenkins; Celine Marcus (86-1117-86), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2995)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, New York - Reports, Publications - Joseph Jenkins; Celine Marcus (86-1117-86), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2996)
    - University Settlement - Administration - Lew Smith (87-1153-87), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2997)
    - University Settlement - Application - Lew Smith (87-1153-87), 1987 (Box 213, Folder 2998)
    - University Settlement - Finance - Lew Smith (87-1153-87), 1987-1988 (Box 213, Folder 2999)
    - Urban Adventures Programs - Administration - Barbara O'Meara (83-0896-00), 1983-1985 (Box 213, Folder 3000)
    - Urban Adventures Programs - Application - Barbara O'Meara (83-0896-00), 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 3001)
    - Urban Adventures Programs - Finance - Barbara O'Meara (83-0896-00), 1983-1984 (Box 213, Folder 3002)
    - Urban Adventures Programs - Reports - Barbara O'Meara (83-0896-00), 1983-1986 (Box 213, Folder 3003)
    - University of Utah - Administration - Arthur Elster, M.D. (84-0958-84), 1986-1989 (Box 214, Folder 3004)
    - University of Utah - Application - Arthur Elster, M.D. (84-0958-84), 1983-1987 (Box 214, Folder 3004)
    - University of Utah - Finance - Arthur Elster, M.D. (84-0958-84), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 3006)
    - University of Utah - Reports - Arthur Elster, M.D. (84-0958-84), 1988 (Box 214, Folder 3007)
    - University of Utah - Reports, Publications - Arthur Elster, M.D. (84-0958-84), 1985-1988 (Box 214, Folder 3008)
    - University of Utah - Arthur Elster, M.D. (84-0958-84), 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 3009)
    - Vacations & Community Services for the Blind - Administration - Linda Watts (83-0902-00), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 3010)
    - Vacations & Community Services for the Blind - Application - Linda Watts (83-0902-00), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 3011)
    - Vacations & Community Services for the Blind - Finance - Linda Watts (83-0902-00), 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 3012)
    - Vacations & Community Services for the Blind - Reports - Linda Watts (83-0902-00), 1984 (Box 214, Folder 3013)
    - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Administration - James M. Perrin, M.D. (82-0836-00), 1983-1985 (Box 214, Folder 3014)
    - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Application - James M. Perrin, M.D. (82-0836-00), 1982-1983 (Box 214, Folder 3015)
    - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Finance - James M. Perrin, M.D. (82-0836-00), 1983-1985 (Box 214, Folder 3016)
    - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Reports, Publications - James M. Perrin, M.D. (82-0836-00), 1988-1992 (Box 214, Folder 3017)
    - Vanderbilt University Medical Center - James M. Perrin, M.D. (82-0836-00), 1982-1985 (Box 214, Folder 3018)
    - University of Virginia - Administration - Robert E. Emery, Ph.D. (85-0897-83), 1983-1986 (Box 214, Folder 3019)
    - University of Virginia - Application - Robert E. Emery, Ph.D. (85-0897-83), 1983-1986 (Box 214, Folder 3020)
    - University of Virginia - Finance - Robert E. Emery, Ph.D. (85-0897-83), 1983-1989 (Box 214, Folder 3021)
    - University of Virginia - Reports - Robert E. Emery, Ph.D. (85-0897-83), 1984-1988 (Box 214, Folder 3022)
    - University of Virginia - Robert E. Emery, Ph.D. (85-0897-83), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 3023)